RG 163, Special Libraries Association, Connecticut Valley Chapter
Connecticut State Library
- Series 2. Administrative Files, 1934-1987
  - 1988-007, 2.0 cubic feet
    - 1979-1980 (Box 3)
      - Correspondence: President, 1979 August-November (Box 3)
      - List of officers, 1979-1980 (Box 3)
      - List of members, 1979 August (Box 3)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 3)
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1980 June-1981 May (Box 3)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1980 June-1981 May (Box 3)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1980 September1981 May (Box 3)
      - Correspondence: Corresponding Secretary, 1980 August (Box 3)
      - List of officers, 1980-1981 (Box 3)
      - List of members, 1980 (Box 3)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 3)
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1981 June-1982 May (Box 3)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1981 Septebmer-1982 May (Box 3)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1981 August-1982 (Box 3)
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1982 April (Box 3)
      - List of members, 1981 (Box 3)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 3)
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1982 June-1983 April (Box 3)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1982 September-1983 May (Box 3)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
      - Annual Reports: Committees, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
      - Correspondence: Corresponding Secretary, 1981 December-1983 May (Box 3)
      - List of members, 1982 (Box 3)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 3)
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1983 June-1984 April (Box 3)
      - Minutes: Business meeting, 1983 September-1984 April (Box 3)
      - Correspondence: Corresponding Secretary, 1983 April (Box 3)
      - List of members, 1983 (Box 3)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 3)
      - Correspondence: Corresponding Secretary, 1984 June-October (Box 3)
      - List of members, 1984 (Box 3)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 3)
      - Minutes and reports: Executive Board, 1986 November-1987 May (Box 3)
      - Annual Reports: Officers, 1987 May (Box 3)
      - Correspondence, 1986 June-1987 April, undated (Box 3)
      - List of officers, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
      - List of members, 1985 February-1987 June (Box 3)
      - Meeting notices, 1986 November-1987 May (Box 3)
      - Long Range Planning Committee, 1987 February, undated (Box 3)
- Series 3. Publications, 1934-1987
  - 1987-042, 1.5 cubic feet
    - Bulletins (Box 5)
      - 1934 September-1943 May (Box 5)
      - 1943 September-1952 July (Box 6)
      - 1952 September-1969 (Box 7)
      - 1970-1987 February (Box 8)
    - Bullet, 1978 August-1981 May (Box 8)
  - 1988-007, 0.25 cubic feet
    - General, 1967 November-1987 (Box 4)
    - Connecticut Library Association publications, 1941-1943, 1970-1973 (Box 4)
    - Special Libraries Association: Newsletter, 1941 Octoer-1987 February (Box 4)
    - Special Libraries Association: Pamphlets, 1937-1987, undated (Box 4)
    - Certificate of Copyright Registration, 1982 (Box 4)
- Series 4. Conferences and Conventions, 1940-1978
  - 1987-042, 0.25 cubic feet
    - Special Libraries Association Conference in Hartford, 1941 (Box 8)
  - 1988-007, 0.5 cubic feet
    - Special Libraries Association Convention in Hartford, 1941 (Box 4)
      - Organization and promotion, 1940 May-1941 June (Box 4)
      - Exhibit refusals, 1941 February-July (Box 4)
      - Publisher's exhibits, 1941 April-August, undated (Box 4)
      - General exhibits, 1941 April-August (Box 4)
      - Exhibit refusals, 1941 February-July, undated (Box 4)
      - News clippings, 1941 April-June (Box 4)
      - Gazette, 1941 June (Box 4)
      - Post-conference correspondence, 1941 June-July, undated (Box 4)
      - Photographs, 1941 June (Box 4)
    - Special Libraries Association Convention, 1975 (Box 4)
      - Correspondence, 1964 March-1965 September (Box 4)
    - Governor's Conference on Library and Information Services, 1978 (Box 5)
      - Pre-Conference information, 1974 December-1978 November (Box 5)
      - Information packet, 1978 December (Box 5)
      - Exhibit information, 1978 (Box 5)
      - Delegate's report, 1978 (Box 5)
      - Photographs, 1978 December (Box 5)
    - Connecticut Valley Chapter 50th Anniversary / Special Libraries Association 75th Anniversary, 1984 (Box 5)
- Series 5. Projects, 1938, 1965, undated; 1988-007; 0.25 cubic feet
  - Special Libraries Exhibit at the Bond Hotel, Hartford, Connecticut, 1938 (Box 5)
  - Seal Project, 1965 April-1967 April (Box 5)
  - Report of Special Libraries Association Education Committee, undated (Box 5)
- Series 6. Union Lists and Bibliographies, 1940-1942, 1962-1971; 1988-007; 0.25 cubic feet
  - Bibliography of the Industrial and Financial History of Connecticut, 1940 May (Box 5)
  - Special Collections in Connecticut and Western Massachusetts, 1941 (Box 5)
  - National Defense Basic Book for Industrial Training, 1942 May (Box 5)
  - Union List of Serials, undated (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, 1962 June-1971 April, undated (Box 5)
  - Special Collections in Connecticut Libraries, undated (Box 5)
- Series 7. Legislation, 1945-1947; 1988-007; 0.25 cubic feet
  - Legislation, 1945-1947 (Box 5)
- Series 8. News Clippings, 1936-1949; 1988-007; 0.25 cubic feet (Box 5)
  - News clippings, 1936 May-1949 September (Box 5)
- Series 9. Photographs, 1940-1993; 1988-007; 0.25 cubic feet
  - Photographs, 1940-1993 (Box 5)
- Series 10. Memorabilia, 1984; 1988-007; 0.25 cubic feet
  - Special Libraries Association 75th anniversary paperweight, 1984 (Box 5)
  - Connecticut Valley Chapter 50th Anniversary guest book, 1984 May 17 (Box 5)